<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<results>
  -<result>
    <quote>"Everything should be made as simple as possible, but not simpler.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>"I want to know Gods thoughts.... all the rest are just details</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>"Imagination is more important than knowledge.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>"My life is a simple thing that would interest no one. It is a known fact that I was born and that is all that is necessary.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>"My religion consists of a humble admiration of the illimitable superior spirit who reveals himself in the slight details we are able to perceive with our frail and feeble mind.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>...One of the strongest motives that lead men to art and science is escape from everyday life with its painful crudity and hopeless dreariness, from the fetters of one's own ever-shifting desires. A finely tempered nature longs to escape from the personal life into the world of objective perception and thought.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A human being is part of a whole, called by us the 'Universe,' a part limited in time and space. He experiences himself, his thoughts and feelings, as something separated from the rest--a kind of optical delusion of his consciousness. This delusion is a kind of prison for us, restricting us to our personal desires and to affection for a few persons nearest us. Our task must be to free ourselves from this prison by widening our circles of compassion to embrace all living creatures and the whole of nature in its beauty.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A human being is part of a whole, called by us the Universe, a part limited in time and space. He experiences himself, his thoughts and feelings, as something separated from the rest--a kind of optical delusion of his consciousness. This delusion is a kind of prison for us, restricting us to our personal desires and to affection for a few persons nearest us. Our task must be to free ourselves from this prison by widening our circles of compassion to embrace all living creatures and the whole of nature in its beauty.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A hundred times every day I remind myself that my inner and outer life depends on the labors of other men, living and dead, and that I must exert myself in order to give in the measure as I have received and am still receiving.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A man's ethical behavior should be based effectually on sympathy, education, and social ties no religious basis is necessary. Man would indeed be in a poor way if he had to be restrained by fear of punishment and hope of reward after death.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A person starts to live when he can live outside himself.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A photograph never grows old. You and I change, people change all through the months and years, but a photograph always remains the same. How nice to look at a photograph of mother or father taken many years ago. You see them as you remember them. But as people live on, they change completely. That is why I think a photograph can be kind.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A storm broke loose in my mind.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A theory can be proved by experiment but no path leads from experiment to the birth of a theory.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>After a certain high level of technical skill is achieved, science and art tend to coalesce in esthetics, plasticity, and form. The greatest sceintists are always artists as well.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All of us who are concerned for peace and triumph of reason and justice must be keenly aware how small an influence reason and honest good will exert upon events in the political field.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All our thoughts and concepts are called up by sense-experiences and have a meaning only in reference to these sense-experiences. On the other hand, however, they are products of the spontaneous activity of our minds they are thus in no wise logical consequences of the contents of these sense-experiences. If, therefore, we wish to grasp the essence of a complex of abstract notions we must for the one part investigate the mutual relationships between the concepts and the assertions made about them for the other, we must investigate how they are related to the experiences.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>An empty stomach is not a good political advisor.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Anger dwells only in the bosom of fools.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Any intelligent fool can make things bigger and more complex ... it takes a touch of genius -- and a lot of courage -- to move in the opposite direction.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Any intelligent fool can make things bigger, more complex, and more violent. It takes a touch of genius -- and a lot of courage -- to move in the opposite direction.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Any power must be an enemy of mankind which enslaves the individual by terror and force, whether it arises under the Fascist or the Communist flag. All that is valuable in human society depends upon the opportunity for development accorded to the individual.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>As far as the laws of mathematics refer to reality, they are not certain and as far as they are certain, they do not refer to reality.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>As far as the laws of mathematics refer to reality, they are not certain, and as far as they are certain, they do not refer to reality.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>As far as the laws of mathematics refer to reality, they are not certain; and as far as they are certain, they do not refer to reality.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>As long as Nazi violence was unleashed only, or mainly, against the Jews, the rest of the world looked on passively and even treaties and agreements were made with the patently criminal government of the Third Reich.... The doors of Palestine were closed to Jewish immigrants, and no country could be found that would admit those forsaken people. They were left to perish like their brothers and sisters in the occupied countries. We shall never forget the heroic efforts of the small countries, of the Scandinavian, the Dutch, the Swiss nations, and of individuals in the occupied part of Europe who did all in their power to protect Jewish lives.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>As long as there are sovereign nations possessing great power, war is inevitable.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>At any rate, I am convinced that He God does not play dice.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Before God we are all equally wise - and equally foolish.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Bias against the Negro is the worst disease from which the society of our nation suffers.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>By academic freedom I understand the right to search for truth and to publish and teach what one holds to be true. This right implies also a duty one must not conceal any part of what on has recognized to be true. It is evident that any restriction on academic freedom acts in such a way as to hamper the dissemination of knowledge among the people and thereby impedes national judgment and action.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Common sense is that layer of prejudices which we acquire before we are sixteen.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Common sense is the collection of prejudices acquired by age eighteen.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Computers are incredibly fast, accurate, and stupid. Human beings are incredibly slow, inaccurate, and brilliant. Together they are powerful beyond imagination.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Concern for man himself and his fate must always form the chief interest of all technical endeavor. Never forget this in the midst of your diagrams and equations.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Concern for man himself and his fate must always form the chief interest of all technical endeavors, concern for the great unsolved problems of the organization of labor and the distribution of goods--in order that the creations of our mind shall be a blessing and not a curse to mankind. Never forget this in the midst of your diagrams and equations.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Do not worry about your difficulties in Mathematics. I can assure you mine are still greater.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Do not worry about your problems in mathematics. I assure you, my problems with mathematics are much greater than yours.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Each of us visits this Earth involuntarily, and without an invitation. For me, it is enough to wonder at the secrets.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything one learned in school.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Emc (Energy equals mass times the square of the speed of light.) Original statement If a body gives off the energy L in the form of radiation, its mass diminshes by Lc.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Ethical axioms are found and tested not very differently from the axioms of science. Truth is what stands the test of experience.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Every kind of peaceful cooperation among men is primarily based on mutual trust and only secondarily on institutions such as courts of justice and police.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Everything is determined, the beginning as well as the end, by forces over which we have no control. It is determined for insects as well as for the stars. Human beings, vegetables or cosmic dust, we all dance to a mysterious tune, intoned in the distance by an invisible piper.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Everything should be made as simple as possible, but not one bit simpler.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Everything should be made as simple as possible, but not simpler.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Everything that is really great and inspiring is created by the individual who can labor in freedom.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Few are those who see with their own eyes and feel with their own hearts.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Few people are capable of expressing with equanimity opinions which differ from the prejudices of their social environment. Most People are even incapable of forming such opinions.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Few people are capable of expressing with equanimity opinions which differ from the prejudices of their social environment. Most people are not even capable of forming such opinions.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Generations to come will find it difficult to believe that a man such as Gandhi ever walked the face of this earth.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Generations to come will scarce believe that such a one as this ever in flesh and blood walked upon this earth. (said of Mahatma Gandhi)</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>God does not care about our mathematical difficulties. He integrates empirically.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>God may be subtle, but He isn't mean.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>God reveals himself in the orderly harmony of what exists.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Gravitation can not be held responsible for people falling in love.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Gravitation cannot be held responsible for people falling in love.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Great spirits have always encountered violent opposition from mediocre minds.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Great spirits have always found violent opposition from mediocrities. The latter cannot understand it when a man does not thoughtlessly submit to hereditary prejudices but honestly and courageously uses his intelligence.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who can no longer pause to wonder and stand rapt in awe, is as good as dead his eyes are closed.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who cherishes the values of culture cannot fail to be a pacifist.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who joyfully marches in rank and file has already earned my contempt. He has been given a large brain by mistake, since for him the spinal cord would suffice.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who joyfully marches to music in rank and file has already earned my contempt. He has been given a large brain by mistake, since for him the spinal cord would fully suffice. This disgrace to civilization should be done away with at once. Heroism at command, senseless brutality, and all the loathsome nonsense that goes by the name of patriotism, how violently I hate all this, how despicable and ignoble war is I would rather be torn to shreds than be part of so base an action It is my conviction that killing under the cloak of war is nothing but an act of murder.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who joyfully marches to music in rank and file has already earned my contempt. He has been given a large brain by mistake, since for him the spinal cord would fully suffice. This disgrace to civilization should be done away with at once. Heroism at command, senseless brutality, deplorable patriotism, how violently I hate all this, how despicable and ignoble war is; I would rather be torn to shreds than be part of so base an action! It is my conviction that killing under the cloak of war is nothing but an act of murder.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who joyfully marches to music rank and file, has already earned my contempt. He has been given a large brain by mistake, since for him the spinal cord would surely suffice. This disgrace to civilization should be done away with at once. Heroism at command, how violently I hate all this, how despicable and ignoble war is; I would rather be torn to shreds than be a part of so base an action. It is my conviction that killing under the cloak of war is nothing but an act of murder.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Heroism on command, senseless violence, and all the loathsome nonsense that goes by the name of patriotism -- how passionately I hate them!</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Heroism on command, senseless violence, and all the loathsome nonsense that goes by the name of patriotism -how passionately I hate them</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How I wish that somewhere there existed an island for those who are wise and of goodwill In such a place even I would be an ardent patriot.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How strange is the lot of us mortals Each of us is here for a brief sojourn for what purpose he knows not, though he senses it. But without deeper reflection one knows from daily life that one exists for other people.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Human beings are not condemned, because of their biological constitution, to annihilate each other or to be at the mercy of a cruel, self-inflicted fate.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am absolutely convinced that no wealth in the world can help humanity forward, even in the hands of the most devoted worker. The example of great and pure individuals is the only thing that can lead us to noble thoughts and deeds. Money only appeals to selfishness and irresistibly invites abuse. Can anyone imagine Moses, Jesus or Ghandi armed with the money-bags of Carnegie</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am enough of an artist to draw freely upon my imagination. Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I believe that whoever tries to think things through honestly will soon recognize how unworthy and even fatal is the traditional bias against Negroes. What can the man of good will do to combat this deeply rooted prejudice He must have the courage to set an example by words and deed, and must watch lest his children become influenced by racial bias.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I believe that whoever tries to think things through honestly will soon recognize how unworthy and even fatal is the traditional bias against Negroes. What can the man of good will do to combat this deeply rooted prejudice? He must have the courage to set an example by words and deed, and must watch lest his children become influenced by racial bias.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not believe in the immortality of the individual, and I consider ethics to be an exclusively human concern without any superhuman authority behind it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not believe that civilization will be wiped out in a war fought with the atomic bomb. Perhaps two-thirds of the people of the Earth might be killed, but enough men capable of thinking, and enough books, would be left to start again, and civilization could be restored.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I don't know how man will fight World War III, but I do know how they will fight World War IV with sticks and stones.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I don't know what kind of weapons will be used in the third world war, assuming there will be a third world war. But I can tell you what the fourth world war will be fought with -- stone clubs.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I don't know what will be used in the next world war, but the 4th will be fought with stones.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I feel that you are justified in looking into the future with true assurance, because you have a mode of living in which we find the joy of life and the joy of work harmoniously combined. Added to this is the spirit of ambition which pervades your very being, and seems to make the day's work like a happy child at play. (referring to America)</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have become rather like King Midas, except that everything turns not into gold but into a circus.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have deep faith that the principle of the universe will be beautiful and simple.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have reached an age when, if someone tells me to wear socks, I don't have to.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I know not with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with sticks and stones.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I like neither new clothes nor new kinds of food.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I live in that solitude which is painful in youth, but delicious in the years of maturity.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I never came upon any of my discoveries through the process of rational thinking.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I never think of the future - it comes soon enough.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I never think of the future. It comes soon enough.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I think and think for months and years. Ninety-nine times, the conclusion is false. The hundredth time I am right.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I want to know how God created this world. I am not interested in this or that phenomenon, in the spectrum of this or that element. I want to know His thoughts the rest are details.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If a cluttered desk signs a cluttered mind, of what, then, is an empty desk a sign</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If A equals success, then the formula is A equals X plus Y plus Z. X is work. Y is play. Z is keep your mouth shut.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If A is success in life, then A equals x plus y plus z. Work is x y is play and z is keeping your mouth shut.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I had only known, I would have been a locksmith.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I were to start taking care of my grooming, I would no longer be my own self ... so the hell with it ... I will continue to be unconcerned about it, which surely has the advantage that I'm left in peace by many a fop who would otherwise come to see me.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If most of us are ashamed of shabby clothes and shoddy furniture, let us be more ashamed of shabby ideas and shoddy philosophies.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If my theory of relativity is proven successful, Germany will claim me as a German and France will declare that I am a citizen of the world.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If my theory of relativity proves to be correct, Germany will claim me a German, and France will claim me a citizen of the world. However, if it proves wrong, France will say I'm a German, and Germany will say that I'm a jew.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If people are good only because they fear punishment, and hope for reward, then we are a sorry lot indeed.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If the facts don't fit the theory, change the facts.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it?</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If you are out to describe the truth, leave elegance to the tailor.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If you can't explain it simply, you don't understand it well enough.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal. Not to people or things.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Imagination is more important than knowledge.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Imagination is more important than knowledge...</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In light of knowledge attained, the happy achievement seems almost a matter of course, and any intelligent student can grasp it without too much trouble. But the years of anxious searching in the dark, with their intense longing, their alterations of confidence and exhaustion and the final emergence into the light -- only those who have experienced it can understand it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In order to form an immaculate member of a flock of sheep one must, above all, be a sheep.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Innumerable voices have been asserting for some time now that human society is passing through a crisis, that its stability has been gravely shattered. It is characteristic of such a situation that individuals feel indifferent or even hostile toward the group, small or large, to which they belong. In order to illustrate my meaning, let me record here a personal experience. I recently discussed with an intelligent and well-disposed man the threat of another war, which in my opinion would seriously endanger the existence of mankind, and I remarked that only a supranational organization would offer protection from that danger. Thereupon my visitor, very calmly and coolly, said to me Why are you so deeply opposed to the disappearance of the human race</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Insanity doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Intellectual growth should commence at birth and cease only at death.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Intellectuals solve problems geniuses prevent them.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It has become appallingly obvious that our technology has exceeded our humanity.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is characteristic of the military mentality that nonhuman factors (atom bombs, strategic bases, weapons of all sorts, the possession of raw materials, etc) are held essential, while the human being, his desires, and thoughts - in short, the psychological factors - are considered as unimportant and secondary...The individual is degraded...to "human materiel".</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is in fact nothing short of a miracle that the modern methods of instruction have not yet entirely strangled the holy curiosity of inquiry for what this delicate little plant needs more than anything, besides stimulation, is freedom. It is a very grave mistake to think that the enjoyment of seeing and searching can be promoted by means of coercion and a sense of duty.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is in fact nothing short of a miracle that the modern methods of instruction have not yet entirely strangled the holy curious of inquiry. It is a very grave mistake to think that the enjoyment of seeing and searching can be promoted by means of coercion and a sense of duty.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is mathematics that offers the exact natural sciences a certain measure of security which, without mathematics, they could not attain.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is not the fruits of scientific research that elevate man and enrich his nature. but the urge to understand, the intellectual work, creative or receptive.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is only to the individual that a soul is given.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the duty of every citizen according to his best capacities to give validity to his convictions in political affairs.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the supreme art of the teacher to awaken joy in creative expression and knowledge.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the theory that decides what we can observe.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It would be a sad situation if the wrapper were better than the meat wrapped inside it. (referring to clothing)</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Laws alone can not secure freedom of expression in order that every man present his views without penalty there must be spirit of tolerance in the entire population.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Laws alone can not secure freedom of expression; in order that every man present his views without penalty there must be spirit of tolerance in the entire population.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Let every man be respected as an individual and no man idolized.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Make everything as simple as possible, but not simpler. A man should look for what is, and not for what he thinks should be. We cannot solve our problems with the same thinking we used when we created them. A question that sometimes drives me hazy: am I or are the others crazy? Any intelligent fool can make things bigger and more complex... It takes a touch of genius - and a lot of courage to move in the opposite direction. All religions, arts and sciences are branches of the same tree. It's not that I'm so smart, it's just that I stay with problems longer. </quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Make everything as simple as possible, but not simpler.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>More and more I come to value charity and love of one's fellow being above everything else... All our lauded technological progress--our very civilization--is like the axe in the hand of the pathological criminal.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Most people go on living their everyday life half frightened, half indifferent, they behold the ghostly tragi-comedy that is being performed on the international stage before the eyes and ears of the world.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My life is a simple thing that would interest no one. It is a known fact that I was born and that is all that is necessary.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My pacifism is an instinctive feeling, a feeling that possesses me because the murder of men is disgusting. My attitude is not derived from any intellectual theory but is based on my deepest antipathy to every kind of cruelty and hatred.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My religion consists of a humble admiration of the illimitable superior spirit who reveals himself in the slight details we are able to perceive with our frail and feeble mind.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My religion consists of a humble admiration of the unlimitable superior who reveals Himself in the slight details we are able to perceive with our frail and feeble minds. That deeply emotional conviction of the presence of a superior reasoning power, which is revealed in the incomprehensible universe, forms my idea of God</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My religion consists of a humble admiration of the unlimitable superior who reveals Himself in the slight details we are able to perceive with our frail and feeble minds. That deeply emotional conviction of the presence of a superior reasoning power, which is revealed in the incomprehensible universe, forms my idea of God.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My sense of God is my sense of wonder about the Universe.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nationalism is an infantile disease. It is the measles of mankind.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never regard study as a duty but as an enviable opportunity to learn to know the liberating influence of beauty in the realm of the spirit for your own personal joy and to the profit of the community to which your later works belong.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never regard study as a duty, but as the enviable opportunity to learn to know the liberating influence of beauty in the realm of the spirit for your own personal joy and to the profit of the community to which your later work belongs.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>No amount of experimentation can ever prove me right a single experiment can prove me wrong.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>No amount of experimentation can ever prove me right; a single experiment can prove me wrong.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>No, this trick won't work...How on earth are you ever going to explain in terms of chemistry and physics so important a biological phenomenon as first love</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Not everything that can be counted counts, and not everything that counts can be counted.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Not everything that counts can be counted, and not everything that can be counted counts.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Not until we dare to regard ourselves as a nation, not until we respect ourselves, can we gain the esteem of others, or rather only then will it come of its own accord.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nothing is more destructive of respect for the government and the law of the land than passing laws which cannot be enforced. It is an open secret that the dangerous increase of crime in this counrty is closely related with this.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Now he has departed from this strange world a little ahead of me. That means nothing. People like us, who believe in physics, know that the distinction between past, present, and future is only a stubbornly persistent illusion.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Of all the communities available to us there is not one I would want to devote myself to, except for the society of the true searchers, which has very few living members at any time.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Of what significance is one's one existence, one is basically unaware. What does a fish know about the water in which he swims all his life The bitter and the sweet come from outside. The hard from within, from one's own efforts. For the most part I do what my own nature drives me to do. It is embarrassing to earn such respect and love for it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One had to cram all this stuff into one's mind for the examinations, whether one liked it or not. This coercion had such a deterring effect on me that, after I had passed the final examination, I found the consideration of any scientific problems distasteful to me for an entire year.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One should guard against preaching to young people success in the customary form as the main aim in life. The most important motive for work in school and in life is pleasure in work, pleasure in its result, and the knowledge of the value of the result to the community.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Only a life lived for others is a life worth while.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Only a life lived for others is a life worthwhile.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Only one who devotes himself to a cause with his whole strength and soul can be a true master. For this reason mastery demands all of a person.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Only two things are infinite, the universe and human stupidity, and I'm not sure about the former.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Our defense is not in our armaments, nor in science, nor in going underground. Our defense is in law and order.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Peace cannot be kept by force. It can only be achieved by understanding.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>People like us, who believe in physics, know that the distinction between past, present, and future is only a stubbornly persistent illusion.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Physical concepts are free creations of the human mind, and are not, however it may seem, uniquely determined by the external world.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Put your hand on a hot stove for a minute, and it seems like an hour. Sit with a pretty girl for an hour, and it seems like a minute. THAT'S relativity.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Quantum mechanics is certainly imposing. But an inner voice tells me that it is not yet the real thing. The theory says a lot, but does not really bring us closer to the secret of the 'Old One.' I, at any rate, am convinced that He is not playing at dice.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Reading, after a certain age, diverts the mind too much from its creative pursuits. Any man who reads too much and uses his own brain too little falls into lazy habits of thinking.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Relativity applies to physics, not ethics.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Science is a wonderful thing if one does not have to earn one's living at it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Science without religion is lame, religion without science is blind.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Since I do not foresee that atomic energy is to be a great boon for a long time, I have to say that for the present it is a menace. Perhaps it is well that it should be. It may intimidate the human race into bringing order into its international affairs, which, without the pressure of fear, it would not do.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Since that deluge of newspaper articles I have been so flooded with questions, invitations, suggestions, that I keep dreaming I am roasting in Hell, and the mailman is the devil eternally yelling at me, showering me with more bundles of letters at my head because I have not answered the old ones.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>So long as there are men there will be wars.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Something deeply hidden had to be behind things.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Sometimes one pays most for the things one gets for nothing.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Teaching should be such that what is offered is perceived as a valuable gift and not as a hard duty.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Technological progress is like an axe in the hands of a pathological criminal.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The aim (of education) must be the training of independently acting and thinking individuals who, however, can see in the service to the community their highest life achievement.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The American lives even more for his goals, for the future, than the European. Life for him is always becoming, never being.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The attempt to combine wisdom and power has only rarely been successful and then only for a short while.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The conscientious objector is a revoultionary. On deciding to disobey the law he sacrifices his personal interests to the most important cause of working for the betterment of society.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The crippling of individuals I consider the worst evil of capitalism. Our whole educational system suffers from this evil. An exaggerated competitive attitude is inculcated into the student, who is trained to worship acquisitive success as a perparation for his future career.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The difference between stupidity and genius is that genius has its limits.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The difference between what the most and the least learned people know is inexpressibly trivial in relation to that which is unknown.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The eternal mystery of the world is its comprehensibility.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The fear of death is the most unjustified of all fears, for there's no risk of accident for someone who's dead.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The further the spiritual evolution of mankind advances, the more certain it seems to me that the path to genuine religiosity does not lie through the fear of life, and the fear of death, and blind faith, but through striving after rational knowledge.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The grand aim of all science is to cover the greatest number of empirical facts by logical deduction from the smallest number of hypotheses or axioms.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The hardest thing in the world to understand is the income tax.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The hardest thing to understand in the world is the income tax.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The highest destiny of the individual is to serve rather than to rule.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The human mind is not capable of grasping the Universe. We are like a little child entering a huge library. The walls are covered to the ceilings with books in many different tongues. The child knows that someone must have written these books. It does not know who or how. It does not understand the languages in which they are written. But the child notes a definite plan in the arrangement of the books - a mysterious order which it does not comprehend, but only dimly suspects.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The ideals which have always shone before me and filled me with the joy of living are goodness, beauty, and truth. To make a goal of comfort or happiness has never appealed to me; a system of ethics built on this basis would be sufficient only for a herd of cattle.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The ideals which have lighted my way, and time after time have given me new courage to face life cheerfully, have been Kindness, Beauty, and Truth. The trite subjects of human efforts, possessions, outward success, luxury have always seemed to me contemptible.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The important thing is not to stop questioning.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The important thing is not to stop questioning. Curiosity has its own reason for existing.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The important thing is not to stop questioning. Curiosity has its own reason for existing. One cannot help but be in awe when he contemplates the mysteries of eternity, of life, of the marvelous structure of reality. It is enough if one tries merely to comprehend a little of this mystery every day. Never lose a holy curiosity.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The individual must not merely wait and criticize, he must defend the cause the best he can. The fate of the world will be such as the world deserves.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The Lord God is subtle, but malicious He is not.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The man who regards his own life and that of his fellow creatures as meaningless is not merely unhappy but hardly fit for life.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The mere formulation of a problem is far more essential than its solution, which may be merely a matter of mathematical or experimental skills. To raise new questions, new possibilities, to regard old problems from a new angle requires creative imagination and marks real advances in science.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most beautiful and most profound emotion we can experience is the sensation of the mystical. It is the sower of all true science. So to whom this emotion is a stranger, who can no longer wonder and stand rapt in awe, is as good as dead. To know that which is impenetretrable to us really exists, manifesting itself as the highest wisdom and the most radiant beauty which our dull faculties can comprehend only in their primitive forms-this knowledge, this feeling is at the center of true religiousness.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most beautiful experience we can have is the mysterious - the fundamental emotion which stands at the cradle of true art and true science.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious. It is the source of all true art and all science. He to whom this emotion is a stranger, who can no longer pause to wonder and stand rapt in awe, is as good as dead his eyes are closed.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious. It is the source of all true art and all science. He to whom this emotion is a stranger, who can no longer pause to wonder and stand rapt in awe, is as good as dead: his eyes are closed.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious. It is the source of all true art and science.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>
      The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious.<br> It is the source of all art and science.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most incomprehensible thing about the world is that it is at all comprehensible.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The most incomprehensible thing about the world is that it is comprehensible.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The only real valuable thing is intuition.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The only reason for time is so that everything doesn't happen at once.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The only thing that interferes with my learning is my education.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The physicist cannot simply surrender to the philosopher the critical contemplation of the theoretical foundations for he himself knows best and feels most surely where the shoe pinches.... he must try to make clear in his own mind just how far the concepts which he uses are justified... The whole of science is nothing more than a refinement of everyday thinking.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The point is to develop the childlike inclination for play and the childlike desire for recognition and to guide the child over to important fields for society. Such a school demands from the teacher that he be a kind of artist in his province.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The problems that exist in the world today cannot be solved by the level of thinking that created them.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The process of scientific discovery is, in effect, a continual flight from wonder.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The pursuit of truth and beauty is a sphere of activity in which we are permitted to remain children all our lives.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The release of atomic energy has not created a new problem. It has merely made more urgent the necessity of solving an existing one.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The secret to creativity is knowing how to hide your sources.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The significant problems we face cannot be solved at the same level of thinking we were at when we created them.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The state exists for man, not man for the state. The same may be said of science. These are old phrases, coined by people who saw in human individuality the highest human value. I would hesitate to repeat them, were it not for the ever recurring danger that they may be forgotten, especially in these days of organization and stereotypes.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The strength of the Constitution lies entirely in the determination of each citizen to defend it. Only if every single citizen feels duty bound to do his share in this defense are the constitutional rights secure.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The tragedy of life is what dies in the hearts and souls of people while they live.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The true measure of a man is the degree to which he has managed to subjugate his ego.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The unleashed power of the atom has changed everything save our modes of thinking and we thus drift toward unparalleled catastrophe.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The value of a man resides in what he gives and not in what he is capable of receiving.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The wirless telegraph is not difficult to understand. The ordinary telegraph is like a very long cat. You pull the tail in New York, and it meows in Los Angeles. The wireless is the same, only without the cat.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The world is a dangerous place to live, not because of the people who are evil, but because of the people who don't do anything about it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Theories should be as simple as possible, but not simpler.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are two ways of resisting war: the legal way and the revolutionary way. The legal way involves the offer of alternatinve service not as a privilege for a few but as a right for all. The revolutionary view involves an uncompromising resistance, with a view to breaking the power of militarism in time of peace or the resources of the state in time of war.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There comes a time when the mind takes a higher plane of knowledge but can never prove how it got there.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There has already been published by the bucketfuls such brazen lies and utter fictions about me that I would long since have gone to my grave if I had let myself pay attention to that.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There is an atmosphere of well-sounding oratory that likes to attach itself to dress clothes. Away with it</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There was this huge world out there, independent of us human beings and standing before us like a great, eternal riddle, at least partly accessible to our inspection and thought. The contemplation of that world beckoned like a liberation.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Those people have seen something. What it is I do not know and I can not care to know. (on flying saucers)</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To know that what is impenetrable to us really exists, manifesting itself as the highest wisdom and the most radiant beauty, which our dull facilities can comprehend only in the most primitive forms--this knowledge, this feeling, is at the center of true religiousness. In this sense, and in this sense only, I belong to the ranks of the devoutly religious men.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To my mind to kill in war is not a whit better than to commit ordinary murder.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To my mind, to kill in war is not a whit better than to commit ordinary murder.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To punish me for my contempt for authority, fate made me an authority myself.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Too many of us look upon Americans as dollar chasers. This is a cruel libel, even if it is reiterated thoughtlessly by the Americans themselves.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>True art is characterized by an irresistible urge in the creative artist</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>True art is characterized by an irresistible urge in the creative artist.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Truth is what stands the test of experience.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Try not to become a man of success but rather to become a man of value.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Try not to become a man of success but rather try to become a man of value.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Try not to become a man of success, but rather try to become a man of value.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We believe that an informed citizenry will act for life and not for death. (on atomic energy)</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We cannot dispair of humanity, since we are ourselves human beings.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We cannot solve our problems with the same thinking we used when we created them.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We scientists, whose tragic destiny it has been to make the methods of annihilation ever more gruesome and more effective, must consider it our solemn and transcendent duty to do all in our power in preventing these weapons from being used for the brutal purpose for which they were invented.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We should take care not to make the intellect our god it has, of course, powerful muscles, but no personality.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We should take care not to make the intellect our god; it has, of course, powerful muscles, but no personality.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We still do not know one thousandth of one percent of what nature has revealed to us.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We still do not know one-thousandth of one percent of what nature has revealed to us.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We [Jews] have no other means of self-defense than our solidarity</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Weakness of attitude becomes weakness of character.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What is inconceivable about the universe is that it is at all conceivable.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What is the meaning of human life, or of organic life altogether To answer this question at all implies a religion. Is there any sense then, you ask, in putting it I answer, the man who regards his own life and that of his fellow creatures as meaningless is not merely unfortunate but almost disqualified for life.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What really interests me is whether God had any choice in the creation of the world.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When all think alike, no one thinks very much.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I examine myself and my methods of thought, I come to the conclusion that the gift of fantasy has meant more to me than any talent for abstract, positive thinking.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I examine myself and my methods of thought, I come to the conclusion that the gift of fantasy has meant more to me than my talent for absorbing positive knowledge.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When the Special Theory of Relativity began to germinate in me, I was visited by all sorts of nervous conflicts... I used to go away for weeks in a state of confusion.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When you are courting a nice girl an hour seems like a second. When you sit on a red-hot cinder a second seems like an hour. That's relativity.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When you look at yourself from a universal standpoint, something inside always reminds or informs you that there are bigger and better things to worry about.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Where the world ceases to be the scene of our personal hopes and wishes, where we face it as free beings admiring, asking and observing, there we enter the realm of Art and Science.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Whoever is careless with the truth in small matters cannot be trusted with important matters.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Whoever undertakes to set himself up as a judge of Truth and Knowledge is shipwrecked by the laughter of the Gods.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why does this magnificent applied science, which saves work and makes life easier, bring us little happiness The simple answer runs because we have not yet learned to make sensible use of it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why is it that nobody understands me and everybody likes me</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Wisdom is not a product of schooling, but of the life- long attempt to acquire it.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Yes, we have to divide up our time like that, between our politics and our equations. But to me our equations are far more important, for politics are only a matter of present concern. A mathematical equation stands forever.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You cannot simultaneously prevent and prepare for war.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You see, wire telegraph is a kind of a very, very long cat. You pull his tail in New York and his head is meowing in Los Angeles. Do you understand this And radio operates exactly the same way you send signals here, they receive them there. The only difference is that there is no cat.</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>Did blind chance know that there was light and what was its refraction, and fit the eyes of all creatures after the most curious manner to make use of it? These and other suchlike considerations, always have, and always will prevail with mankind, to believe that there is a Being who made all things, who has all things in his power, and who is therefore to be feared.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not know what I may appear to the world but to myself I seem to have been only like a boy playing on the seashore, and diverting myself in now and then finding a smoother pebble or a prettier shell than ordinary, whilst the great ocean of truth lay all undiscovered before me.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not know what I may appear to the world; but to myself I seem to have been only like a boy playing on the sea shore and diverting himself and then finding a smoother pebble or a prettier shell that ordinary while the greater ocean of truth lay all undiscovered before me.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I keep the subject of my inquiry constantly before me, and wait till the first dawning opens gradually, by little and little, into a full and clear light.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I seem to have been like a child playing on the sea shore, finding now and then a prettier shell than ordinary, whilst the great ocean of truth lay undiscovered before me.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I was like a boy playing on the sea-shore, and diverting myself now and then finding a smoother pebble or a prettier shell than ordinary, whilst the great ocean of truth lay all undiscovered before me.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I have ever made any valuable discoveries, it has been owing more to patient attention, than to any other talent.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I have seen further it is by standing on the shoulders of giants.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I have seen further, it is by standing on the shoulders of giants.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>A coward is incapable of exhibiting love; it is the prerogative of the brave.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A man is but the product of his thoughts. What he thinks, he becomes.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Adaptability is not imitation. It means power of resistance and assimilation.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Always aim at complete harmony of thought and word and deed. Always aim at purifying your thoughts and everything will be well.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Among the many misdeeds of the British rule in India, history will look upon the act of depriving a whole nation of arms as the blackest.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>An eye for an eye makes the whole world blind.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>An eye for eye only ends up making the whole world blind.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>As long as you derive inner help and comfort from anything, keep it.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Freedom is not worth having if it does not include the freedom to make mistakes.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Hate the sin, love the sinner.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Honest differences are often a healthy sign of progress.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Honest disagreement is often a good sign of progress.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am prepared to die, but there is no cause for which I am prepared to kill.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I believe in equality for everyone, except reporters and photographers.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not want my house to be walled in on all sides and my windows to be stuffed. I want the cultures of all the lands to be blown about my house as freely as possible. But I refuse to be blown off my feet by any.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I regard myself as a soldier, though a soldier of peace.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I think it would be a good idea.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I want freedom for the full expression on my personality.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In matters of conscience, the law of majority has no place.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In the attitude of silence the soul finds the path in a clearer light, and what is elusive and deceptive resolves itself into crystal clearness. Our life is a long and arduous quest after Truth.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In the attitude of silence the soul finds the path in an clearer light, and what is elusive and deceptive resolves itself into crystal clearness. Our life is a long and arduous quest after Truth.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Indolence is a delightful but distressing state we must be doing something to be happy.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Indolence is a delightful but distressing state; we must be doing something to be happy.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is better to be violent, if there is violence in our hearts, than to put on the cloak of nonviolence to cover impotence.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the quality of our work which will please God and not the quantity.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is unwise to be too sure of one's own wisdom. It is healthy to be reminded that the strongest might weaken and the wisest might err.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Live as if your were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Live simply that others may simply live.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>N.B. This quote refers to the British disarmament of the Indian Army. Gandhi never advocated the individual right to bear arms.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One needs to be slow to form convictions, but once formed they must be defended against the heaviest odds.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The future depends on what we do in the present.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The good man is the friend of all living things.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The only devils in this world are those running around in our own hearts, and that is where all our battles should be fought.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The only tyrant I accept in this world is the still voice within.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The outward freedom that we shall attain will only be in exact proportion to the inward freedom to which we may have grown at a given moment. And if this is a correct view of freedom, our chief energy must be concentrated on achieving reform from within.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are seven sins in the world: Wealth without work, Pleasure without conscience, Knowledge without character, Commerce without morality, Science without humanity, Worship without sacrifice and politics without principle.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There is more to life than increasing its speed</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To conceal ignorance is to increase it. An honest confession of it, however, gives ground for the hope that it will diminish some day or the other.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Victory attained by violence is tantamount to a defeat, for it is momentary.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We must become the change we want to see.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What difference does it make to the dead, the orphans and the homeless, whether the mad destruction is wrought under the name of totalitarianism or the holy name of liberty or democracy</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Whatever you do will be insignificant, but it is very important that you do it.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I despair, I remember that all through history the ways of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants, and murderers, and for a time they can seem invincible, but in the end they always fall. Think of it - always.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Where there is love there is life.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You must be the change you want to see in the world.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You must be the change you wish to see in the world.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You must not lose faith in humanity. Humanity is an ocean if a few drops of the ocean are dirty, the ocean does not become dirty.</quote>
    <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
  </result>
    <result>
      <quote>Your beliefs become your thoughts. Your thoughts become your words. Your words become your actions. Your actions become your habits. Your habits become your values. Your values become your destiny.</quote>
      <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>
    </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>Purity,patience, and preserverance are the three essentials to success, and above all love.</quote>
    <author>Swami Vivekananda</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>This world is the great gymnasium where we come to make ourselves strong.</quote>
    <author>Swami Vivekananda</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Three things are necessary to make every man great,every nation great1.Conviction of the powers of goodness.2.Absence of jealousy and suspicion.3.Helping all who are trying to be and do good.</quote>
    <author>Swami Vivekananda</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>A large income is the best recipe for happiness I ever heard of.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>But when a young lady is to be a heroine, the perverseness of forty surrounding families cannot prevent her. Something must and will happen to throw a hero in her way.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Everybody likes to go their own way--to choose their own time and manner of devotion.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>For what do we live, but to make sport for our neighbors and laugh at them in our turn?</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Friendship is certainly the finest balm for the pangs of disappointed love.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I cannot think well of a man who sports with any woman's feelings and there may often be a great deal more suffered than a stander-by can judge of.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not want people to be agreeable, as it saves me that trouble of liking them.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not want people to be agreeable, as it saves me the trouble of liking them.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I pay very little regard...to what any young person says on the subject of marriage. If they profess a disinclination for it, I only set it down that they have not yet seen the right person.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If any one faculty of our nature may be called more wonderful than the rest, I do think it is memory. There seems something more speakingly incomprehensible in the powers, the failures, the inequalities of memory, than in any other of our intelligences. The memory is sometimes so retentive, so serviceable, so obedient at others, so bewildered and so weak and at others again, so tyrannic, so beyond control We are, to be sure, a miracle every way but our powers of recollecting and of forgetting do seem peculiarly past finding out.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In every power, of which taste is the foundation, excellence is pretty fairly divided between the sexes.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is always incomprehensible to a man that a woman should ever refuse an offer of marriage.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It will, I believe, be everywhere found, that as the clergy are, or are not what they ought to be, so are the rest of the nation.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nothing amuses me more than the easy manner with which everybody settles the abundance of those who have a great deal less than themselves.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Oh do not attack me with your watch. A watch is always too fast or too slow. I cannot be dictated to by a watch.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One cannot be always laughing at a man without now and then stumbling on something witty.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One cannot fix one's eyes on the commonest natural production without finding food for a rambling fancy.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One does not love a place the less for having suffered in it unless it has all been suffering, nothing but suffering.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One half of the world can not understand the pleasures of the other.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One half of the world cannot understand the pleasures of the other.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Silly things do cease to be silly if they are done by sensible people in an impudent way.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The enthusiasm of a woman's love is even beyond the biographer's.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There is not one in a hundred of either sex who is not taken in when they marry . It is, of all transactions, the one in which people expect most from others, and are least honest themselves.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There will be little rubs and disappointments everywhere, and we are all apt to expect too much but then, if one scheme of happiness fails, human nature turns to another if the first calculation is wrong, we make a second better we find comfort somewhere.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Those who do not complain are never pitied.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To sit in the shade on a fine day, and look upon verdure is the most perfect refreshment.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We have all a better guide in ourselves, if we would attend to it, than any other person can be.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We met Dr. Hall in such deep mourning that either his mother, his wife, or himself must be dead.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What dreadful hot weather we have! It keeps me in a continual state of inelegance.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What dreadful weather we have! It keeps me in a continual state of inelegance.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Where any one body of educated men, of whatever denomination, are condemned indiscriminately, there must be a deficiency of information, or...of something else.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Where so many hours have been spent in convincing myself that I am right, is there not some reason to fear I may be wrong</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Where so many hours have been spent in convincing myself that I am right, is there not some reason to fear I may be wrong?</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why not seize the pleasure at once, how often is happiness destroyed by preparation, foolish preparations.</quote>
    <author>Jane Austen</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>...happiness is the highest good, being a realization and perfect practice of virtue, which some can attain, while others have little or none of it...</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A flatterer is a friend who is your inferior, or pretends to be so.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A friend is a second self.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A great city is not to be confounded with a populous one.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A likely impossibility is always preferable to an unconvincing possibility.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A state is not a mere society, having a common place, established for the prevention of mutual crime and for the sake of exchange...Political society exists for the sake of noble actions, and not of mere companionship.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A whole is that which has beginning, middle and end.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Again, men in general desire the good, and not merely what their fathers had.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All human actions have one or more of these seven causes chance, nature, compulsion, habit, reason, passion, and desire.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All human actions have one or more of these seven causes: chance, nature, compulsion, habit, reason, passion, and desire.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All men by nature desire knowledge.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All paid jobs absorb and degrade the mind.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All proofs rest on premises.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>All virtue is summed up in dealing justly.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Anyone can become angry. That is easy. But to be angry with the right person, to the right degree, at the right time, for the right purpose and in the right way - that is not easy.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Both oligarch and tyrant mistrust the people, and therefore deprive them of their arms.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Change in all things is sweet.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Character is that which reveals moral purpose, exposing the class of things a man chooses or avoids</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Consider pleasures as they depart, not as they come.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Courage is the first of human qualities because it is the quality which guarantees the others.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Different men seek after happiness in different ways and by different means, and so make for themselves different modes of life and forms of government.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Dignity consists not in possessing honors, but in the consciousness that we deserve them.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Dignity does not consist in possessing honors, but in deserving them.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Education and morals will be found almost the whole that goes to make a good man.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Education is the best provision for old age.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Education is the best provision for the journey to old age.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Even when laws have been written down, they ought not always to remain unaltered.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Evil draws men together.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Excellence is an art won by training and habituation. We do not act rightly because we have virtue or excellence, but we rather have those because we have acted rightly. We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act but a habit.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>For the things we have to learn before we can do them, we learn by doing them.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Happiness depends upon ourselves.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Happiness is a state of activity.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Happiness is the meaning and the purpose of life, the whole aim and end of human existence.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who cannot be a good follower cannot be a good leader.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He who is unable to live in society, or who has no need because he is sufficient for himself, must be either a beast or a god.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Hope is a waking dream.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Humor is the only test of gravity, and gravity of humor for a subject which will not bear raillery is suspicious, and a jest which will not bear serious examination is false wit.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Humor is the only test of gravity, and gravity of humor; for a subject which will not bear raillery is suspicious, and a jest which will not bear serious examination is false wit.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I count him braver who conquers his desires than him who conquers his enemies for the hardest victort is the victory over self.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I count him braver who overcomes his desires than him who overcomes his enemies.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have gained this by philosophy that I do without being commanded what others do only from fear of the law.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If liberty and equality, as is thought by some are chiefly to be found in democracy, they will be best attained when all persons alike share in the government to the utmost.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In all things of nature there is something of the marvelous.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In poverty and other misfortunes of life men think friends to be their only refuge. The young they keep out of mischief, to the old they are a comfort and aid in their weakness, and those in the prime of life they incite to noble deeds.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In poverty and other misfortunes of life, true friends are a sure refuge. The young they keep out of mischief to the old they are a comfort and aid in their weakness, and those in the prime of life they incite to noble deeds.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In the arena of human life the honours and rewards fall to those who show their good qualities.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is easy to fly into a passion--anybody can do that--but to be angry with the right person and at the right time and with the right object and in the right way--that is not easy, and it is not everyone who can do it.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is in justice that the ordering of society is centered.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is not always the same thing to be a good man and a good citizen.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is possible to fail in many ways...while to succeed is possible only in one way.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is simplicity that makes the uneducated more effective than the educated when addressing popular audiences.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the mark of an educated mind to rest satisfied with the degree of precision which the nature of the subject admits and not to seek exactness where only an approximation is possible.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is the nature of desire not to be satisfied, and most men live only for the gratification of it.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is unbecoming for young men to utter maxims.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is well to be up before daybreak, for such habits contribute to health, wealth, and wisdom.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Law is mind without reason.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Law is order, and good law is good order.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Let us be well persuaded that everyone of us possesses happiness in proportion to his virtue and wisdom, and according as he acts in obedience to their suggestion.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Liars when they speak the truth are not believed.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Man differs from other animals particularly in this, that he is imitative, and acquires his rudiments of knowledge in this way; besides, the delight in imitation is universal.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Man is by nature a political animal.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Man perfected by society is the best of all animals he is the most terrible of all when he lives without law, and without justice.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Man perfected by society is the best of all animals; he is the most terrible of all when he lives without law, and without justice.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Men acquire a particular quality by constantly acting a particular way...you become just by performing just actions, temperate by performing temperate actions, brave by performing brave actions.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Misfortune shows those who are not really friends.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Mothers are fonder than fathers of their children because they are more certain they are their own.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nature does nothing uselessly.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>No great genius has ever existed without some touch of madness.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>No man of high and generous spirit is ever willing to indulge in flattery; the good may feel affection for others, but will not flatter them.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Of all the varieties of virtues, liberalism is the most beloved.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One swallow does not make a summer.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Patience is bitter, but its fruit is sweet.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Philosophy is the science which considers truth.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Piety requires us to honor truth above our friends.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Poverty is the parent of revolution and crime.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Probable impossibilities are to be preferred to improbable possibilities.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The aim of art is to represent not the outward appearance of things, but their inward significance.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The basis of a democratic state is liberty.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The best friend is the man who in wishing me well wishes it for my sake.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The best political community is formed by citizens of the middle class.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The educated differ from the uneducated as much as the living from the dead.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The gods too are fond of a joke</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The gods too are fond of a joke.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The high minded man must care more for the truth than for what people think.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The ideal man bears the accidents of life with dignity and grace, making the best of circumstances.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The least deviation from truth will be multiplied later.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The least initial deviation from the truth is multiplied later a thousandfold.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The only stable state is the one in which all men are equal before the law.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The ridiculous is produced by any defect that is unattended by pain, or fatal consequences; thus, an ugly and deformed countenance does not fail to cause laughter, if it is not occasioned by pain.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The wicked have no stability, for they do not remain in consistency with themselves; they continue friends only for a short time, rejoicing in each other?s wickedness.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There was never a genius without a tincture of madness.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>They should rule who are able to rule best.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>This communicating of a man's self to his friend works two contrary effects for it redoubleth joys, and cutteth griefs in half.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Those that know, do. Those that understand, teach.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Those who educate children well are more to be honored than parents, for these only gave life, those the art of living well.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Those who have the command of the arms in a country are masters of the state, and have it in their power to make what revolutions they please. Thus, there is no end to observations on the difference between the measures likely to be pursued by a minister backed by a standing army, and those of a court awed by the fear of an armed people.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Time crumbles things everything grows old under the power of Time and is forgotten through the lapse of Time.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To be conscious that we are perceiving or thinking is to be conscious of our own existence.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To enjoy the things we ought and to hate the things we ought has the greatest bearing on excellence of character.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To give a satisfactory decision as to the truth it is necessary to be rather an arbitrator than a party to the dispute.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To love someone is to identify with them.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To perceive is to suffer.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To Thales the primary question was not what do we know, but how do we know it.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We are what we repeatedly do.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act but a habit.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act, but a habit.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We make war that we may live in peace.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We must as second best...take the least of the evils.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Well begun is half done.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What is a friend A single soul dwelling in two bodies.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What lies in our power to do, it lies in our power not to do.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What we have to learn to do, we learn by doing.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Whatsoever that be within us that feels, thinks, desires, and animates, is something celestial, divine, and, consequently, imperishable.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Wishing to be friends is quick work, but friendship is slow-ripening fruit.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Wit is educated insolence.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>With regard to excellence, it is not enough to know, but we must try to have and use it.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Without friends no one would choose to live, though he had all other goods.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Young people are in a condition like permanent intoxication, because youth is sweet and they are growing.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Youth is easily deceived because it is quick to hope.</quote>
    <author>Aristotle</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>As the poet said, 'Only God can make a tree' -- probably because it's so hard to figure out how to get the bark on.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>At the opera in Milan with my daughter and me, Needleman leaned out of his box and fell into the orchestra pit. Too proud to admit it was a mistake, he attended the opera every night for a month and repeated it each time.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Basically my wife was immature. I'd be at home in the bath and she'd come in and sink my boats.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Bisexuality automatically doubles your chances for a date on Saturday night.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Bisexuality immediately doubles your chances for a date on Saturday night.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Dying is one of the few things that can be done as easily lying down.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Eighty percent of success is showing up.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Eternal nothingness is fine if you happen to be dressed for it.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Eternity is a long time, especially towards the end.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>For a while we pondered whether to take a vacation or get a divorce. We decided that a trip to Bermuda is over in two weeks, but a divorce is something you always have.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>For the first year of marriage I had basically a bad attitude. I tended to place my wife underneath a pedestal</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>His lack of education is more than compensated for by his keenly developed moral bankruptcy.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How can I believe in God when just last week I got my tongue caught in the roller of an electric typewriter</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How can I believe in God when just last week I got my tongue caught in the roller of an electric typewriter?</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How is it possible to find meaning in a finite world, given my waist and shirt size</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How is it possible to find meaning in a finite world, given my waist and shirt size?</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>How to make God laugh: Tell him your future plans.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am at two with nature.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I call that mind free which jealously guards its intellectual rights and powers, which calls no man master, which does not content itself with a passive or hereditary faith, and receives new truth as an angel from Heaven.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I can't listen to that much Wagner. I start getting the urge to conquer Poland.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I don't want to achieve immortality through my work... I want to achieve it through not dying.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I had a terrible education. I attended a school for emotionally disturbed teachers.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I tended to place my wife under a pedestal.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I took a speed reading course and read 'War and Peace' in twenty minutes. It involves Russia.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I took a speed-reading course and read War and Peace in twenty minutes. It involves Russia.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I was thrown out of college for cheating on the metaphysics exam I looked into the soul of the boy sitting next to me.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I was thrown out of college for cheating on the metaphysics exam; I looked into the soul of the boy sitting next to me.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I will not eat oysters. I want my food dead- not sick, not wounded - dead.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I will not eat oysters. I want my food dead. Not sick -- not wounded -- dead.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I will not eat oysters. I want my food dead. Not sick, not wounded: dead.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I'm astounded by people who want to 'know' the universe when it's hard enough to find your way around Chinatown.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If it turns out that there is a God, I don't think that he's evil. But the worst that you can say about him is that basically he's an underachiever.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If only God would give me some clear sign Like making a large deposit in my name in a Swiss bank.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If only God would give me some clear sign! Like making a large deposit in my name in a Swiss bank.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If you're not failing every now and again, it's a sign you're not doing anything very innovative.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Interestingly, according to modern astronomers, space is finite. This is a very comforting thought - particularly for people who cannot remember where they left things.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Interestingly, according to modern astronomers, space is finite. This is a very comforting thought -- particularly for people who can never remember where they have left things.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Interestingly, according to modern astronomers, space is finite. This is a very comforting thought-- particularly for people who can never remember where they have left things.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Interestingly, according to modern astronomers, space is finite. This is a very comforting thought---particularly for people who can never remember where they have left things.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Is sex dirty? Only if you do it right.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is impossible to experience one's death objectively and still carry a tune.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is impossible to travel faster than the speed of light, and certainly not desirable, as one's hat keeps blowing off.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is no secret that organized crime in America takes in over forty billion dollars a year. This is quite a profitable sum, especially when one considers that the Mafia spends very little for office supplies.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It seemed the world was divided into good and bad people. The good ones slept better... while the bad ones seemed to enjoy the waking hours much more.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Life is divided into the horrible and the miserable.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Life is full of misery, loneliness, and suffering - and it's all over much too soon.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Love is the answer, but while you are waiting for the answer, sex raises some pretty good questions.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>More than any other time in history, mankind faces a crossroads. One path leads to despair and utter hopelessness. The other, to total extinction. Let us pray we have the wisdom to choose correctly.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>More than any time in history mankind faces a crossroads. One path leads to despair and utter hopelessness, the other to total extinction. Let us pray that we have the wisdom to choose correctly.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>More than any time in history mankind faces a crossroads. One path leads to utter hopelessness and despair, the other to total extinction. Let us hope we have the wisdom to choose correctly.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Most of the time I don't have much fun. The rest of the time I don't have any fun at all.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My one regret in life is that I am not someone else.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Not only is there no God, but try getting a plumber on weekends.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nothing worth knowing can be understood with the mind.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>On the plus side, death is one of the few things that can be done just as easily lying down.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Organized crime in America takes in over forty billion dollars a year and spends very little on office supplies.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Seventy percent of success in life is showing up.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Sex alleviates tension. Love causes it.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Should I marry W. Not if she won't tell me the other letters in her name.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Students achieving Oneness will move on to Twoness.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The good people sleep much better at night than the bad people. Of course, the bad people enjoy the waking hours much more.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The government is unresponsive to the needs of the little man. Under 5'7, it is impossible to get your congressman on the phone.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The great roe is a mythological beast with the head of a lion and the body of a lion, though not the same lion.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The lion and the calf shall lie down together but the calf won't get much sleep.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are three rings involved with marriage. The engagement ring, the wedding ring, and the suffering.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are worse things in life than death. Have you ever spent an evening with an insurance salesman</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are worse things in life than death. Have you ever spent an evening with an insurance salesman?</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Thought Why does man kill He kills for food. And not only food frequently there must be a beverage.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Thought: Why does man kill? He kills for food. And not only food: frequently there must be a beverage.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To you I'm an atheist to God, I'm the Loyal Opposition.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We were married by a reformed rabbi in Long Island. A very reformed rabbi. A Nazi.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What if everything is an illusion and nothing exists In that case, I definitely overpaid for my carpet.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What if everything is an illusion and nothing exists? In that case, I definitely overpaid for my carpet.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What if nothing exists and we're all in somebody's dream Or what's worse, what if only that fat guy in the third row exists</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I was in school, I cheated on my metaphysics exam I looked into the soul of the boy sitting next to me.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I was kidnapped, my parents snapped into action. They rented out my room.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why are our days numbered and not, say, lettered</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why are our days numbered and not, say, lettered?</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You can live to be a hundred if you give up all the things that make you want to live to be a hundred.</quote>
    <author>Woody Allen</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>And the work of righteousness shall be peace and the effect of righteousness quietness and assurance for ever.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Ask, and it shall be given you Seek, and ye shall find Knock, and it shall be opened unto you.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Blessed is the man that endureth temptation for when he is tried, he shall receive the crown of life.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Do not envy a sinner you don't know what disaster awaits him.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Do to others what you would have them do to you.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Faith is the substance of things hoped for, the evidence of things not seen.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Faith without works is dead.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Forsake not an old friend for the new is not comparable to him a new friend is as new wine when it is old, thou shalt drink it with pleasure.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Prove all things hold fast that which is good.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The patient in spirit is better than the proud in spirit.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The source of the famous Golden Rule. Many famous lines were variations on this theme.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Ye shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free.</quote>
    <author>Bible</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>Don't confuse being 'soft' with seeing the other guy's point of view.</quote>
    <author>George Bush</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have opinions of my own -- strong opinions -- but I don't always agree with them.</quote>
    <author>George Bush</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>'But it is always interesting when one doesn't see,' she added. 'If you don't see what a thing means, you must be looking at it wrong way around.'</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>An archaeologist is the best husband any woman can have the older she gets, the more interested he is in her.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Curious things, habits. People themselves never knew they had them.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Good advice is always certain to be ignored, but that's no reason not to give it.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I don't think necessity is the mother of invention - invention, in my opinion, arises directly from idleness, possibly also from laziness. To save oneself trouble.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have enjoyed greatly the second blooming that comes when you finish the life of the emotions and of personal relations and suddenly find - at the age of fifty, say - that a whole new life has opened before you, filled with things you can think about, study, or read about...It is as if a fresh sap of ideas and thoughts was rising in you.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have enjoyed greatly the second blooming... suddenly you find - at the age of 50, say - that a whole new life has opened before you.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have enjoyed greatly the second bloomingsuddenly you find - at the age of 50, say - that a whole new life has opened before you.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have sometimes been wildly, despairingly, acutely miserable ... but through it all I still know quite certainly that just to be alive is a grand thing.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I live now on borrowed time, waiting in the anteroom for the summons that will inevitably come. And then - I go on to the next thing, whatever it is. One doesn't luckily have to bother about that.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If one sticks too rigidly to one's principles, one would hardly see anybody.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is a curious thought, but it is only when you see people looking ridiculous that you realize how much you love them.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never do anything yourself that others can do for you.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One is left with the horrible feeling now that war settles nothing that to win a war is as disastrous as to lose one.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Where large sums of money are concerned, it is advisable to trust nobody.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Your travel life has the aspect of a dream. It is something outside the normal, yet you are in it. It is peopled with characters you have never seen before and in all probability will never see again. It brings occasional homesickness, and loneliness, and pangs of longing... But you are like the Vikings who have gone into a world of adventure, and home is not home until you return.</quote>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>A cat will look down to a man. A dog will look up to a man. But a pig will look you straight in the eye and see his equal.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A fanatic is one who can't change his mind and won't change the subject.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A lie gets halfway around the world before the truth has a chance to get its pants on.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A love of tradition has never weakened a nation, indeed it has strengthened nations in their hour of peril but the new view must come, the world must roll forward.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>
      A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; <br> an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Although prepared for martyrdom, I preferred that it be postponed.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>An appeaser is one who feeds a crocodile, hoping it will eat him last.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Any man who is under 30, and is not a liberal, has not heart and any man who is over 30, and is not a conservative, has no brains.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Broadly speaking, the short words are the best, and the old words best of all.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Dictators ride to and fro upon tigers which they dare not dismount. And the tigers are getting hungry.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Don't talk to me about naval tradition. It's nothing but rum, sodomy and the lash.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Every day you may make progress. Every step may be fruitful. Yet there will stretch out before you an ever-lengthening, ever-ascending, ever-improving path. You know you will never get to the end of the journey. But this, so far from discouraging, only adds to the joy and glory of the climb.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Everyone has his day and some days last longer than others.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Fanatic. One who can't change his mind and won't change the subject.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>For myself I am an optimist - it does not seem to be much use being anything else.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>For myself I am an optimist--it does not seem to be much use being anything else.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>From now on, ending a sentence with a preposition is something up with which I will not put.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>From Stettin in the Baltic to Trieste in the Adriatic an iron curtain has descended across the Continent.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Golf is a game whose aim is to hit a very small ball into a even smaller hole, with weapons singularly ill- designed for the purpose.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>He has all the virtues I dislike and none of the vices I admire.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Here is the answer which I will give to President Roosevelt... We shall not fail or falter we shall not weaken or tire. Neither the sudden shock of battle nor the long-drawn trials of vigilance and exertion will wear us down. Give us the tools and we will finish the job.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>History will be kind to me for I intend to write it.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am certainly not one of those who need to be prodded. In fact, if anything, I am the prod.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am prepared to meet my Maker. Whether my Maker is prepared for the great ordeal of meeting me is another matter.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am ready to meet my Maker. Whether my Maker is prepared for the great ordeal of meeting me is another matter.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I am reminded of the professor who, in his declining hours, was asked by his devoted pupils for his final counsel. He replied, 'Verify your quotations.'</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I cannot forecast to you the action of Russia. It is a riddle wrapped in a mystery inside an enigma but perhaps there is a key. That key is Russian national interest.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I cannot forecast to you the action of Russia. It is a riddle wrapped in a mystery inside an enigma.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I cannot pretend to feel impartial about colours. I rejoice with the brilliant ones and am genuinely sorry for the poor browns.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I gather, young man, that you wish to be a Member of Parliament. The first lesson that you must learn is, when I call for statistics about the rate of infant mortality, what I want is proof that fewer babies died when I was Prime Minister than when anyone else was Prime Minister. That is a political statistic.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have always felt that a politician is to be judged by the animosities he excites among his opponents.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have nothing to offer but blood, toil, tears and sweat.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I like pigs. Dogs look up to us. Cats look down on us. Pigs treat us as equals.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I would say to the House, as I said to those who have joined this Government 'I have nothing to offer but blood, toil, tears, and sweat.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Immature love says, I love you because I need you, mature love says, I need you because I love you.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In my belief, you cannot deal with the most serious things in the world unless you also understand the most amusing.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It has been said that democracy is the worst form of government except all the others that have been tried.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is a good thing for an uneducated man to read books of quotations. Bartlett's Familiar Quotations is an admirable work, and I studied it intently. The quotations when engraved upon the memory give you good thoughts. They also make you anxious to read the authors and look for more.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is a mistake to try to look too far ahead. The chain of destiny can only be grasped one link at a time.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is a socialist idea that making profits is a vice. I consider the real vice is making losses.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is better to be making the news than taking it to be an actor rather than a critic.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is no use saying We are doing our best. You have got to succeed in doing what is necessary.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Kites rise highest against the wind - not with it.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Kites rise highest against the wind---not with it.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Let us therefore brace ourselves to our duty, and so bear ourselves that, if the British Commonwealth and the Empire last for a thousand years, men will still say, This was their finest hour.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Many forms of Government have been tried, and will be tried in this world of sin and woe. No one pretends that democracy is perfect or all-wise. Indeed, it has been said that democracy is the worst form of government except all those other forms that have been tried from time to time.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Men occasionally stumble on the truth, but most of them pick themselves up and hurry off as if nothing had happened.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Men stumble over the truth from time to time, but most pick themselves up and hurry off as if nothing happened.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Mr Attlee is a very modest man. Indeed he has a lot to be modest about.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My wife and I tried to breakfast together, but we had to stop or our marriage would have been wrecked.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never give in, never give in, never, never, never, never -- in nothing, great or small, large or petty -- never give in except to convictions of honor and good sense.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never hold discussions with the monkey when the organ grinder is in the room.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never in the field of human conflict was so much owed by so many to so few.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Never, never, never believe any war will be smooth and easy, or that anyone who embarks on the strange voyage can measure the tides and hurricanes he will encounter. The statesman who yields to war fever must realize that once the signal is given, he is no longer the master of policy but the slave of unforeseeable and uncontrollable events.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nothing in life is so exhilarating as to be shot at without result.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Now this is not the end. It is not even the beginning of the end. But it is, perhaps, the end of the beginning.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One day President Roosevelt told me that he was asking publicly for suggestions about what the war should be called. I said at once 'The Unnecessary War'.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>One ought never to turn one's back on a threatened danger and try to run away from it. If you do that, you will double the danger. But if you meet it promptly and without flinching, you will reduce the danger by half.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Personally I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>So they the Government go on in strange paradox, decided only to be undecided, resolved to be irresolute, adamant for drift, solid for fluidity, all-powerful to be impotent.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Solitary trees, if they grow at all, grow strong.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Success is never final.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Success is not final, failure is not fatal it is the courage to continue that counts.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Success is the ability to go from failure to failure without losing your enthusiasm.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Success is the ability to go from one failure to another with no loss of enthusiasm.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The British nation is unique in this respect. They are the only people who like to be told how bad things are, who like to be told the worst.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The empires of the future are the empires of the mind.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The greatest lesson in life is to know that even fools are right sometimes.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The heights of great men reached and kept, Were not attained by sudden flight, But they, while their companions slept, Were toiling upwards in the night.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The inherent vice of capitalism is the unequal sharing of blessings the inherent virtue of socialism is the equal sharing of miseries.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The maxim of the British people is 'Business as Usual.'</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The power of man has grown in every sphere, except over himself.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The price of greatness is responsibility.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The reserve of modern assertions is sometimes pushed to extremes, in which the fear of being contradicted leads the writer to strip himself of almost all sense and meaning.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The substance of the eminent Socialist gentleman's speech is that making a profit is a sin, but it is my belief that the real sin is taking a loss.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are a terrible lot of lies going around the world, and the worst of it is half of them are true.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>This report, by its very length, defends itself against being read.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>To build may have to be the slow and laborious task of years. To destroy can be the thoughtless act of a single day.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Too often the strong silent man is silent because he does not know what to say, and is reputed strong only because he has remained silent.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We are all worms, but I do believe that I am a glow-worm.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We make a living by what we get, we make a life by what we give.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We shall defend our island, whatever the cost may be, we shall fight on the beaches, we shall fight on the landing grounds, we shall fight in the fields and in the streets, we shall fight in the hillswe shall never surrender.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We shall not fail or falter we shall not weaken or tire...Give us the tools and we will finish the job.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We shall not flag or fail. We shall go on to the end. We shall fight in France, we shall fight on the seas and the oceans, we shall fight with growing confidence and growing strength in the air, we shall defend our island, whatever the cost may be. We shall fight on the beaches, we shall fight on the landing grounds, we shall fight in the fields and in the streets, we shall fight in the hills we shall never surrender.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We shall show mercy, but we shall not ask for it.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We shape our buildings and they shape us.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We will have no truce or parlay with you Hitler, or the grisly gang who work your wicked will. You do your worst -- and we will do our best.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I am abroad, I always make it a rule never to criticize or attack the government of my own country. I make up for lost time when I come home.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When I look back on all the worries I remember the story of the old man who said on his deathbed that he had a lot of trouble in his life, most of which never happened.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When the eagles are silent, the parrots begin to jabber.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When you get a thing the way you want it, leave it alone.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When you get to the end of your rope tie a knot and hang on.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>When you're going through hell, keep going.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why you may take the most gallant sailor, the most intrepid airman, and th most audacious soldier, put them at a table together-and what do you get? The sum of their fears.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You will make all kinds of mistakes but as long as you are generous and true and fierce you cannot hurt the world, or even seriously distress her.</quote>
    <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>'A merry Christmas, uncle God save you' cried a cheerful voice. 'Bah' said Scrooge. 'Humbug'</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>'At this festive season of the year, Mr Scrooge,' said the gentleman, taking up a pen, 'it is more than usually desirable that we should make some slight provision for the poor and destitute, who suffer greatly at the present time. ... We choose this time, because it is a time, of all others, when Want is keenly felt, and Abundance rejoices.'</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>'Out upon merry Christmas What's Christmas time to you but a time for paying bills without money a time for finding yourself a year older, but not an hour richer... If I could work my will,' said Scrooge indignantly, 'every idiot who goes about with 'Merry Christmas' upon his lips should be boiled with his won pudding, and buried with a stake of holly through his heart. He should'</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>...it was always said of him Scrooge that he knew how to keep Christmas well, if any man alive possessed the knowledge. May that be truly said of us, and all of us</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A loving heart is the truest wisdom.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A man who could build a church, as one may say, by squinting at a sheet of paper.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>A merry Christmas to everybody A happy New Year to all the world</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Accidents will occur in the best regulated families.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Annual income twenty pounds, annual expenditure nineteen six, result happiness. Annual income twenty pounds, annual expenditure twenty pound ought and six, result misery.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Any man may be in good spirits and good temper when he's well dressed. There ain't much credit in that.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>But I am sure that I have always thought of Christmas time, when it has come round...as a good time a kind, forgiving, charitable, pleasant time the only time I know of, in the long calendar of the year, when men and women seem by one consent to open their shut-up hearts freely.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>By the time we hit fifty, we have learned our hardest lessons. We have found out that only a few things are really important. We have learned to take life seriously, but never ourselves.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Cheerfulness and contentment are great beautifiers and are famous preservers of youthful looks.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Have a heart that never hardens, and a temper that never tires, and a touch that never hurts.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Have a heart that never hardens, and a temper that never tries, and a touch that never hurts.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I do not know the American gentleman, god forgive me for putting two such words together.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I have known a vast quantity of nonsense talked about bad men not looking you in the face. Don't trust that conventional idea. Dishonesty will stare honestly out of countenance any day of the week, if there is anything to get got by it.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I never could have done what I have done without the habits of punctuality, order, and diligence, without the determination to concentrate myself on one subject at a time...</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I only ask to be free. The butterflies are free.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I will honor Christmas in my heart, and try to keep it all year.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If a pig could give his mind to anything, he would not be a pig.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In love of home, the love of country has its rise.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>In the little world in which children have their existence, whosoever brings them up, there is nothing so finely perceived and so finely felt, as injustice.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done it is a far, far better rest that I go to, than I have ever known.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It was a turkey He could never have stood upon his legs, that bird He would have snapped 'em off short in a minute, like sticks of sealing wax.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It was the best of times, it was the worst of times it ws the age of wisdom, it was the age of foolishness it was the epoch of belief, it was the epoch of incredulity it was the season of Light, it was the season of Darkness it was the spring of hope, it was the winter of despair we had everything before us, we had nothing before us we were all going directly to Heaven, we were all going the other way.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It was the best of times, it was the worst of times, it was the age of wisdom, it was the age of foolishness, it was the epoch of belief, it was the epoch of incredulity, it was the season of Light, it was the season of Darkness, it was the spring of hope, it was the winter of despair, we had everything before us, we had nothing before us, we were all going direct to heaven, we were all doing direct the other way - in short, the period was so far like the present period, that some of its noisiest authorities insisted on its being received, for good or for evil, in the superlative degree of comparison only.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It was the best of times, it was the worst of times.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Minds, like bodies, will often fall into a pimpled, ill-conditioned state from mere excess of comfort.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>No one is useless in this world who lightens the burdens of another.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Once upon a time--of all the good days in the year, on Christmas Eve--old Scrooge sat busy in his counting-house.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Reflect on your present blessings, of which every man has many not on your past misfortunes, of which all men have some.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Reflect on your present blessings, of which every man has many; not on your past misfortunes, of which all men have some.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Somehow he Tim gets thoughtful sitting by himself so much, and thinks the strangest things you ever heard. He told me, coming home, that he hoped the people saw him in the church, because he was a cripple, and it might be pleasant for them to remember upon Christmas Day, who made lame beggars walk, and blind men see.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Subdue your appetites, my dears, and you've conquered human nature.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The law is sic a ass - a idiot.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Then Bob proposed 'A Merry Christmas to us all, my dears. God bless us' Which all his family re-echoed. 'God bless us every one' said Tiny Tim, the last of all.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There is a wisdom of the head, and ... a wisdom of the heart.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There is always something for which to be thankful.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Train up a fig tree in the way it should go, and when you are old sit under the shade of it.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We need never be ashamed of our tears.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Whatever I have tried to do in life, I have tried with all my heart to do it well whatever I have devoted myself to, I have devoted myself completely in great aims and in small I have always thoroughly been in earnest.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>With affection beaming out of one eye, and calculation shining out of the other.</quote>
    <author>Charles Dickens</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>(Miele) really thought the process through. They did such a great job designing these washers and dryers. I got more thrill out of them than I have out of any piece of high tech in years.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Apple has some tremendous assets, but I believe without some attention, the company could, could, could -- I'm searching for the right word -- could, could die.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Do you want to spend the rest of your life selling sugared water or do you want a chance to change the world?</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Do you want to spend the rest of your life selling sugared water or do you want a chance to change the world?</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Focus is about saying, No. And the result of that focus is going to be some really great products where the total is much greater than the sum of the parts.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Have the courage to follow your heart and intuition. It’s better to be a pirate than to join the Navy.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I didn't see it then, but it turned out that getting fired from Apple was the best thing that could have ever happened to me. The heaviness of being successful was replaced by the lightness of being a beginner again, less sure about everything. It freed me to enter one of the most creative periods of my life.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I didn't see it then, but it turned out that getting fired from Apple was the best thing that could have ever happened to me. The heaviness of being successful was replaced by the lightness of being a beginner again, less sure about everything. It freed me to enter one of the most creative periods of my life.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I feel like somebody just punched me in the stomach and knocked all my wind out. I'm only 30 years old and I want to have a chance to continue creating things. I know I've got at least one more great computer in me. And Apple is not going to give me a chance to do that.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I think Pixar has the opportunity to be the next Disney -- not replace Disney -- but be the next Disney.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I'm the only person I know that's lost a quarter of a billion dollars in one year.... It's very character-building.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>I've always wanted to own and control the primary technology in everything we do.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I knew in 1986 how much it was going to cost to keep Pixar going, I doubt if I would have bought the company.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>If I were running Apple, I would milk the Macintosh for all it's worth -- and get busy on the next great thing. The PC wars are over. Done. Microsoft won a long time ago.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>IMac is next year's computer for $1,299, not last year's computer for $999.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Innovation has nothing to do with how many R&D dollars you have. When Apple came up with the Mac, IBM was spending at least 100 times more on R&D. It's not about money. It's about the people you have, how you're led, and how much you get it.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It comes from saying no to 1,000 things to make sure we don't get on the wrong track or try to do too much.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It is hard to think that a $2 billion company with 4,300-plus people couldn't compete with six people in blue jeans.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It wasn't that Microsoft was so brilliant or clever in copying the Mac, it's that the Mac was a sitting duck for 10 years. That's Apple's problem: Their differentiation evaporated.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It will go down in history as a turning point for the music industry. This is landmark stuff. I can't overestimate it!</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It'll make your jaw drop.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It's better to be a pirate than to join the Navy.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It's rare that you see an artist in his 30s or 40s able to really contribute something amazing.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>It's really hard to design products by focus groups. A lot of times, people don't know what they want until you show it to them.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>My opinion is that the only two computer companies that are software-driven are Apple and NeXT, and I wonder about Apple.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Nobody has tried to swallow us since I've been here. I think they are afraid how we would taste.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The cure for Apple is not cost-cutting. The cure for Apple is to innovate its way out of its current predicament.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The desktop computer industry is dead. Innovation has virtually ceased. Microsoft dominates with very little innovation. That's over. Apple lost. The desktop market has entered the dark ages, and it's going to be in the dark ages for the next 10 years, or certainly for the rest of this decade.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The Japanese have hit the shores like dead fish. They're just like dead fish washing up on the shores.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The products suck! There's no sex in them anymore!</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>The subscription model of buying music is bankrupt. I think you could make available the Second Coming in a subscription model and it might not be successful.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>There are sneakers that cost more than an iPod.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We believe it's the biggest advance in animation since Walt Disney started it all with the release of Snow White 50 years ago.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>We made the buttons on the screen look so good you'll want to lick them.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>What's new is this amazingly efficient distribution system for stolen property called the internet -- and no one's gonna shut down the internet.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Why would I ever want to run Disney? Wouldn't it make more sense just to sell them Pixar and retire?</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>You know, I've got a plan that could rescue Apple. I can't say any more than that it's the perfect product and the perfect strategy for Apple. But nobody there will listen to me.</quote>
    <author>Steve Jobs</author>
  </result>
  -<result>
    <quote>The great thing about a computer notebook is that no matter how much you stuff into it, it doesn't get bigger or heavier.</quote>
    <author>Bill Gates</author>
  </result>-<result>
    <quote>Your most unhappy customers are your greatest source of learning.</quote>
    <author>Bill Gates</author>
  </result>
  
</results>